

# ADARSH MORE

WEB DESIGNER

## **CONTACT DETAILS**

- +971 558 831 375
- Jebel Ali, Dubai, UAE
- ✓ adarshmore888@gmail.com
- www.behance.net/adarshmore

## **SKILLS**

HTML	
CSS	
BOOTSTRAP	1111111
WORDPRESS	
WEBFLOW	
SHOPIFY	
WIX	
KAJABI	
ILLUSTRATOR	1111111
PHOTOSHOP	
FIGMA	

#### **ABOUT ME**

As an experienced Web designer, I specialize in creating visually appealing and functional websites that meet the needs of clients and end-users. With expertise in HTML, CSS, and Wordpress, Webflow, Shopify, Wix, I am able to develop responsive designs that are optimized for all devices.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor Of Arts**

Savitribai Phule Pune University.

## **Graphics And Web Design**

Excellent Multimedia Pune

# **Higher Secondary School**

CSR College Jategaon BK. Pune.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Joseph Engineering Services**

2023 - Current

UAE based company where my role is to develop website on various platform like wordpress, Webflow, etc.

# **Breakfree Marketing LLP**

2022 - 23

Working for USA clients my role is design and develop website as per clients requirement and help Junior designers for design and development.

# **AffinityX**

2019 - 22

MNC based company where my role is to design and develop the website from scratch as per the clients requirement with using Html, css, Photoshop, Figma, etc.

#### LANGUAGE

MARATHI				
ENGLISH	1			
HINDI				